<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WitherCubes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WitherCubes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Physics - Light</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/physics-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/physics-light/</guid>
      <description>Light     Optics    It&amp;rsquo;s a branch of physics which describes about phenomenon and laws associated with generation and propagation of light, its interaction with the matter called optics.
Optics are classified into two types
 Ray Optics Physical Optics  Ray Optics     It treats the propagation of light in terms of rays and is valid if only the wavelength of the light is much smaller than the size of the obstacle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure the Firefox Web Browser</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/secure-firefox/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/secure-firefox/</guid>
      <description>Most Firefox users think that firefox has security and privacy features out of the box. The answer is that it&amp;rsquo;s certainly better compared to other mainstream alternatives (like Microsoft Edge, Google Chrome).
Why do people trust that Firefox more in terms of security and privacy than Google Chrome? The answer is simple because Firefox is a Free and Open Source Software. This means that anyone can audit the code of firefox and submit bug fixes, exploits to improve firefox and inspect the code if any malicious code is there in the browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Softwate I use</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/software-i-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/software-i-use/</guid>
      <description>Operating System    I use Arch Linux as my operating system. I was once a Windows 10 user but then hated it after knowing how evil it is. I wish I could use Gentoo as my OS but I have a dumb laptop to compile and I love the AUR.
Programs    Web Browser    For my web browser I use Brave. It is better than any proprietary alternatives like Google Chrome, Vivaldi, and Microsoft Edge because Brave doesn&amp;rsquo;t collect user data and sell it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi I am Sanjay Pavan. There is nothing much about me to tell. I am a Linux Enthusiast who learns more about linux day by day. My social links are in homepage. Sometimes I do some shell scripting and dmenu scripting. I am still learning shell scripting so I am not perfect, but here are some of my projects:
 Tuxfetch dmwifi  These are the linux and tech contect creators I recommend you to watch:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
